youplay.com 2007-05-15

# YouPlay - Fun and Games

**Privacy Policy – youplay.com**  
This privacy policy has been created in order to disclose the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site, youplay.com ("Website"). This policy is in addition to the Terms of Use governing the Website and should be read in conjunction with those Terms of Use.

The Website is owned and operated by YouPlay Pty Limited (“YouPlay”), which is a joint venture between Lovatts Interactive Pty Ltd (a division of Lovatts Publications Pty Ltd (“Lovatts”))  and Southern Cross View Pty Ltd which is a wholly owned subsidiary of Southern Cross Broadcasting (Australia) Limited (“Southern Cross Broadcasting”) ("We" and "Us"). You can find out more about us by clicking on links at the bottom of this page. Information provided by you to the Website may be shared amongst and used by these companies, including their subsidiaries and related companies. However, except in the limited circumstances set out below, none of these companies will provide personally identifiable information about you to third parties without your express permission.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
We respect your privacy and will endeavour to ensure your privacy is maintained when providing information electronically.  There are two kinds of information that websites can obtain about you: 

Aggregate Information: Aggregate Information is anonymous data that websites use to analyze trends, administer the Website, diagnose problems on the sites' servers, track user's movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use and to help improve the quality of the web pages. It may derive this information from a domain name or an IP address. None of this information is connected with Personally Identifiable Information.

Personally Identifiable Information: Personally Identifiable Information is any information that personally identifies you. When you become a Website member, we ask you for personal details including name, post code, date of birth, your location, gender and email address. We may also ask you to provide us with some lifestyle information when you register with the Website or for various features of the Website.

Some of the information that we ask you for is mandatory. The primary purposes for which we collect it are:

  * to enable us to identify who is using the service 
  * to enable you to get the most out of the Website 
  * to provide you with casual gameplay online and via other digital media and
  * to provide you with activities and information in relation to YouPlay’s business, Lovatts’ business and Southern Cross Broadcasting’s radio stations, television stations  and other businesses. 

If a question is not specified to be mandatory it is up to you whether or not you answer it.

We also record other information including responses to promotions, give-aways and competitions. Whenever a page is requested from our webserver, we record the time, date and URL of the request, along with information on the browser software that is being used. This information is collected to enable us to better understand the preferences of our members and to enable us to better target our communications including competitions and prizes.

Any information you post on bulletin boards and/or communicated in chat areas and the like on the Website becomes public information. While we strive to protect and respect your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security or treat as personal information any information you disclose in a chat room or bulletin board.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We may share Aggregate Information with companies in the Lovatts group and the Southern Cross Broadcasting group, and our partners, advertisers and sponsors. Personally Identifiable Information about you may be shared in the Lovatts group and the Southern Cross Broadcasting group, and may be shared to external service providers only for the purpose of analysis and the purpose of providing casual gameplay on websites and in digital media.  The Lovatts group will not contact you directly unless you choose to opt-in to receive information about Lovatts.  The Southern Cross Broadcasting group will not contact you directly unless you choose to opt-in to receive information about Southern Cross Broadcasting.

We plan to regularly send a data file to Full Circle Digital, the company that serves advertising on our behalf, containing the following member details of yours: member ID and the DOB, gender, state and postcode that have been provided by you as the member, but not your name and address.  Members supply these details when subscribing to the Website. Full Circle Digital will then use those details only for the purpose of displaying demographically-targeted advertisements to members when you are visiting our website.  They will not be used for any other purpose.  If, however, you would like your personal information not to be used by Full Circle Digital to deliver targeted ads, simply send an email to optout@fullcircledigital.com.

We may disclose personally identifiable information about you to any company in connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, transfer, or exchange of all or a portion of a business or operating unit, but only if that company agrees to use the data prior to any acquisition solely for the purpose of making its acquisition decision and to observe the relevant provisions of our Privacy Policy with respect to the data. We may disclose your personally identifiable information to a particular person or company in the event that that person or company acquires assets from us, and we will require that person or company to agree to observe the relevant provisions of our Privacy Policy with respect to personally identifiable information about you.

We will also disseminate Personally Identifiable Information about you where we believe it is necessary: 

  * because it is required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, cooperate with law enforcement or other government agencies, or comply with a legal process served on the Website or court orders;
  * to provide you with a service which you have requested;
  * to implement our Terms of Use;
  * to protect our rights or property or those of any Website user, or any member of the public.
  * to lessen or prevent a serious threat to a person's health or safety.

Except as described above we will not share your Personally Identifiable Information with any third party without your consent unless we tell you otherwise when asking for it.

**Use of Personal Information**  
In addition to use for the purposes of the disclosures above, we may use your Personally Identifiable Information to: 

  * identify winners of competitions conducted through the Website by posting the names (or user names ) of the winners and their suburb and state of residence;
  * notify you if you are a winner of a competition;
  * where you have agreed, send you information about YouPlay, the Southern Cross Broadcasting group, the Lovatts Group and the Website;
  * where you have agreed, give to our partners, advertisers or sponsors.

**Website Competitions**  
You may wish to enter competitions via the Website. You will be required to provide some Personally Identifiable Information in order to enter each competition. Entries to competitions, which may include Personally Identifiable Information, become the property of the party which is the specified promoter of the competition ("Competition Promoter"). We may be the Competition Promoter, but from time to time, the promoter of the competition may be another company in the Lovatts group or the Southern Cross Broadcasting group or our sponsors or advertisers. Accordingly Personally Identifiable Information will be available to the Competition Promoter for the purpose of administering the competition and notifying you if you are a winner of the competition and for any other purpose to which you specifically agree.

If we are the Competition Promoter, we may make your Personally Identifiable Information available to third parties who have been contracted by Us, for the purpose of administering the competition.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send you site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with you to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to your account via email or phone.

**Storing, Deleting or Modifying Personal Information**  
Please note that we (and third parties to which we provide information) may be required to make copies of or store records (which may include Personally Identifiable Information) in order to comply with our record-keeping obligations under Australian laws.

If you've given us personally identifiable information in the past and wish to access or update that information, you may do so in accordance with the requirements and qualifications in the Privacy Act.

You may:

  * Click on the Update Account button on the Your Account page (accessible via the horizontal navigation bar of the website). Your details will appear in the form you used to register on our website. Please check that your information is accurate and make any required changes then submit your new details by clicking on the Save Changes button at the bottom of the page.

OR

  * Send a letter to:

Youplay Pty Ltd  
Gosford Gateway Centre   
Level 3, 237 Mann St   
Gosford NSW 2250  
Australia

Please note that, unless you notify us otherwise, we will assume that any personal information and preferences in the "My Details" section is correct and up-to-date.

Although it is not always possible to remove or modify information in the databases, we will make reasonable efforts to do so. If you've given us information for a third party (as mentioned above) and we've already passed it on, we cannot delete or change the information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive which may contain information about you, your member status on the website or about websites you have visited. The use of cookies on websites is a common industry standard. Cookies act as unique identifiers, used to distinguish between different users. They can enable us to track and target your interests to enhance your experience on our site and to provide rating information, ad tracking and other functionality normally associated with the delivering of websites. For instance, by setting a cookie on the Website, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Please note that even after we have terminated a cookie, remnants of that cookie may remain on your computer. These remnants are normally inactive.

We use the independent company Nielsen//NetRatings to measure and analyse usage across the Website. The Nielsen//NetRatings SiteCensus tracking code collects the core information on usage of the Website. To learn more about Nielsen//NetRatings' privacy policy, visit their website at <http://www.nielsen-netratings.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs>

One use of cookies on the Website is to allow you to access the members only sections. If you reject the cookie, you may still use the Website. However you will have limited access to the members only areas of the site. For example, you must have access to the members only area to access the competitions.

Various services available to you on the Website will require the use of cookies. We may use cookies when we conduct voting polls, surveys, and contests to limit multiple responses and registrations.

We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site, such as the voting polls, surveys, contest, and game areas, will not function properly if you automatically elect not to receive cookies.

**Spam**  
Spam is the term used to refer to unsolicited electronic messages. We operate an opt-in only policy so we'll only send you commercial electronic messages with your express consent, unless:  
a)         we are communicating with you for one of the purposes we outlined above (you are deemed to be consenting to these communications by accepting the terms of use of the Website);   
b)         we are communicating with you because your friend or contact has asked us to send you a message or invitation and your friend or contact has, to the best of our knowledge, obtained your express consent; or   
c)         we are otherwise permitted by law to send it to you. 

If you are receiving commercial material using the Website or purporting to be connected or associated with the Website, Southern Cross Broadcasting or its subsidiaries, please tell us so that we can take appropriate action.

**Security of Personal Information**  
We've taken precautions to protect your security. These include provisions to preserve the security of the information in our own systems and to prevent unauthorised access, use of disclosure and back-up systems to prevent accidental or malicious loss of data. In addition, employees and contractors who provide services which allow them to access personal information are required to respect the confidentiality of personal information held by YouPlay and Southern Cross Broadcasting.

Unfortunately, there are always risks involved in sending information via electronic means including the Internet and you do it entirely at your own risk.

We will not be responsible for any unauthorised access or use of information held by us. We will also not be responsible if your information is accessed through an unauthorised or improper use of your account or membership privileges due to your failure to adequately secure your password.

When you register on the Website you will create a user name and password. You play an important role in keeping your personal information secure by maintaining the confidentiality of any password and accounts used on the Website.

If you suspect that someone has your user name and password without your express permission, please let us know or change them immediately. You can update your password, including actions that you didn't approve or authorise yourself.

**Links to Third Party Websites**  
This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these or other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects Personally Identifiable Information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

**Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the Website so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use Personally Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email and seek your consent to use the information in a different manner if that is required.

**Questions**  
Questions regarding this policy should be directed in the first instance by writing to us at the following address:  
Youplay Pty Ltd  
Gosford Gateway Centre   
Level 3, 237 Mann St   
Gosford NSW 2250  
Australia

**Additional Privacy Information**  
If you are interested in obtaining additional information on privacy, you can visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's website at [http://www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/)
